[
	{
		"asker": "Bolkoy",
		"question": "How many flowers are in the clearing below this platform?",
		"answer": "13"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Brimstail",
		"question": "What is 19 to the power of 3?",
		"answer": "6859"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Brundt",
		"question": "How many people are waiting for the next bard to perform?",
		"answer": "4"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Cap'n Izzy No-Beard's Parrot",
		"question": "How many banana trees are there in the plantation?",
		"answer": "33"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Caroline",
		"question": "How many fishermen on the fishing platform?",
		"answer": "11, 0 after the quest Salt in the Wound"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Cook",
		"question": "How many cannons does Lumbridge castle have?",
		"answer": "7"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Edmond",
		"question": "How many pigeon cages are there around the back of Jerico's house?",
		"answer": "3"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Gabooty",
		"question": "How many buildings in the village?",
		"answer": "11"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Gnome Ball Referee",
		"question": "What is 57 * 89 + 23?",
		"answer": "5096"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Gnome Coach",
		"question": "How many gnomes on the gnome ball field have red patches on their uniforms?",
		"answer": "6"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Hazlemere",
		"question": "What is 19 to the power of 3?",
		"answer": "6859"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Karim",
		"question": "I have 16 kebabs, I eat one myself and share the rest equally between 3 friends. How many do they have each?",
		"answer": "5"
	},
	{
		"asker": "King Roald",
		"question": "How many bookcases are there in the Varrock palace library?",
		"answer": "24"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Luthas",
		"question": "How many banana trees are there in the plantation?",
		"answer": "33"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Moldark, Emissary of Zamorak",
		"question": "How many bottles are there on the stall to the east of Mr Ex?",
		"answer": "7"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Nials Newton",
		"question": "How many tables are there in the Pick and Lute Inn?",
		"answer": "10"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Oracle",
		"question": "If x is 15 and y is 3, what is 3x + y?",
		"answer": "48"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Recruiter",
		"question": "How many houses have a cross on the door?",
		"answer": "20"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Rommik",
		"question": "How many rocks in the Rimmington mine cannot be used to make bronze?",
		"answer": "7"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Valerio",
		"question": "How many windows in the Abbey courtyard?",
		"answer": "17"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Ysondria",
		"question": "How many ore rocks are there in the nearby copper and tin mine?",
		"answer": "8"
	},
	{
		"asker": "Zoo Keeper",
		"question": "How many animals are in the Ardougne Zoo?",
		"answer": "40, +1 after the quest Eagles' Peak, +1 after Hunt for Red Raktuber."
	}
]